The reason why we are excited is because
access has been granted.
>> Hallelujah.
>> Amen.
>> Access has been
>> granted. And you know when access is
granted, you have a choice to make. You
have a choice either to stay outside or
to come in.
Jesus said, "I am the door.
He who enters will find pasture." And so
the door is opened. Revelation 3:8 says,
"Behold, I open a door before you that
no man can can shut." We say to God be
the glory. And just also celebrating our
sister. We are so glad you could come be
part of us. And um being the first to
open the week is a is favor a big time.
and we bless you. Bless your ministry
that God will increase you and enlarge
you and do you good in this season and
in this time and you need to know that
when you come to things shift
>> and your things have shifted
>> in Jesus name. Amen. Things shift. You
know as I was praying and saying God
what what what what is it you want to
download in the lives of God's people?
What is this you want to download?
And we keep saying that revival is here.
And I want to say this, revival
happens when you know who you are,
what you have, and what you can do.
Revival touches the physical body, it
touches the mind, and it touches the
spirit. The Bible says out of your
innermost being
will flow
rivers of living water that comes from
your spirit. Then it touches your mind.
Then it touches your body. And so the
way you think is going to change. The
way you think is going to change
>> because the rivers flow from inside, not
from outside, from inside. You know
there was a song my sister was singing
that we may be able to deep ourselves in
these waters in this presence of God
which is real which is alive. We know
Pastor Simon that there are many people
who are watching online right now many
of them from many different countries
and they're going to be touched by the
rivers of water that will flow from this
place. something special, something new
is going to happen into their lives
because revival is God's invasion into
our space. And we pray that in Jesus
name that God will do it. Some of those
things he's going to do on his own. And
so you don't have to move God.
He's going to move you.
He's going to do what?
>> To move you. Some of those things are
going to happen suddenly. Some of them
are going to happen during the service
when it the service is go ongoing.
Some of it is going to happen in the
parking lot.
Hallelujah. I suddenly will just hit you
in the name of Jesus. It will happen to
you. Some of you in your car as you're
driving home. For some of you, it's
going to happen to your Uber driver.
Hallelujah.
suddenly will hit him and he will pack
and cry for a few minutes and then
continue the journey. When that happens,
don't be worried. Tell your neighbor,
don't be worried.
>> The presence of God is moving in a very
special way. Hallelujah. And God is
inviting us. Let me read this verse and
then I'll pick up the rest. The Bible
says in Matthew 22, again, this is an
invitation into the presence of God. an
invitation into revival.
The Bible says in Matthew 22, a very
interesting scripture here talking about
the banquet table that God has set for
us. The Bible says Jesus spoke to them
again in parables saying
the kingdom of heaven is like a king who
pray who prepared a wedding banquet for
his son.
He sent his servants to those who had
been invited to the banquet
to tell them to come, but they refused
to come. Then he sent some more servants
and said, "Tell those who have been
invited that I have prepared my dinner.
My oxen and fattened cattle have been
butchered and everything is ready.
Everything is ready. Everything is
ready.
>> Come to the wedding banquet." But they
paid no attention. and went off, one to
his field, another to his business. The
rest seized his servants, mistreated
them, and killed them. The king was
enraged. He sent his army and destroyed
those murderers and burn their city.
Then he said to his servants, "The
wedding banquet is ready." But those
invited did not deserve to come.
So go to the street corners
and invite to the banquet anyone you
find. Tell your neighbor, "Anyone you
find."
>> Anyone you find.
>> So the servants went out into the
streets and gathered all the people they
could find. The bad as well as the good.
And the wedding hall was filled with
guests.
It is my prayer that this week the
banquet will be filled.
>> I'm saying the banquet hall will be
filled.
>> Amen. In the mighty name of Jesus
Christ,
access granted. You have no idea what
that word means. Let me tell you this.
When access is granted, things shift,
things happen. I'm going to talk about
three people here in the Bible. The
first one is Joseph.
And Joseph, access was granted. The
other person I want to talk about is
Esther. Access was granted. And the
third person is the Apostle John. Access
was granted. And you know, God really
wants us to know that he is the one who
opens the door. And that door is Jesus.
Let me read that scripture again in
Philippians 2:5-11.
Talking about this one, in Christ, why
it is so important for you to know that
in Christ access is granted. The Bible
says in your relationships with one
another have the same mindset as Christ
Jesus who being in very nature God did
not consider equality with God something
to be used to his own advantage.
Rather he made himself nothing by taking
the very nature of a servant. Being made
in human likeness and being found in
appearance as a man, he humbled himself
by becoming obedient to death, even
death on a cross. Therefore, God exalted
him to the highest place and gave him
the name, the name, the name,
>> the name,
>> the name that is above every name that
are the name of Jesus,
a few knees.
Baptist knees,
>> knees,
>> Presbyterian knees,
>> Anglican knees,
>> knees,
>> Catholic knees,
>> every knee shall bow
in heaven
and on earth and under the earth. and
every tongue confess and acknowledge
that Jesus Christ is Lord to the glory
of God the Father. I want you to know
that God is not disturbed
when some people oppose him, when some
people fight against him. One thing he
knows very well is this. One day every
knee
>> shall bow,
every tongue confess that Jesus Christ
is Lord to the glory of God the father.
And I want you not to know that when
this access is granted, God is telling
you is that there's nothing that can
stop you.
>> God is saying you are unstoppable in
Jesus name.
The reason why we get stopped is because
not because the door is not open but
because our mind tells us we cannot go
through this door. It is too good for
us. Uh it is too good for us. This place
is too nice. I cannot sit there. You
know there are some hotels you cannot go
into. For example, one of the hotels
that is sponsoring and and just
supporting us is the Sankara uh hotel.
Um, and I can I can vouch right here
that many of you have never stepped
through the gates of Sankara Hotel.
Hello.
Why? It's not because the doors are not
open. Because your mind has told you
that hotel is for people not like you.
Let me tell you this. You don't need to
go to Sankara Hotel just to buy
anything.
And I'm challenging you this week, just
as as you're passing by, just pass by
and and and and and be confident.
Enter that place and be confident. And
as you're entering, after you've given
your phone at the security place and you
pick it on the other side, pick it up
and put it on your ear as if you're
talking to somebody.
Hallelujah.
just walking and says, "Mhm, mhm, yeah.
Yeah. Okay. All right.
I'll get back to you just now. Let me
just talk to these guys on the counter."
And you arrive at the counter and it
says, "Hi guys, I'm so glad to be here
and I would like to ask a few things.
Uh, please, I need your assistance. Um,
but just a minute. Uh, I'm being
called." And then go and sit at the
seat.
Uh, just sit there for a while and just
says, "Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah." and then
go back to the counter and says, "Uh,
I'll come back to you." So, you leave.
You see, you didn't pay anything.
You just walked in
and you walked out, but you walked out
with a testimony that you have been at
Sankara.
Now,
you have no idea that sometimes you can
go in and a miracle happens.
Let me ask you, access is granted.
How many of you are going to go to
Sankara this week?
I've just asked you a question. That's
all I'm asking. You see, you've not
you're not prepared. That the the door
is is open,
but you know, you are still thinking
about it. So, look at your neighbor and
tell your neighbor, "Stop thinking about
it.
And so as I talk about access granted,
you see these are the challenges that
people face. The door is open but people
will still go to hell looking at the
door that is open and think it is too
good for me. I'm not supposed to be
there. Let me tell you this. The banquet
hall is open.
>> The banquet hall is open. The banquet
And you need to change your mindset. You
need to change your mindset. You need to
change how you think because God has
great things for you. Let me tell you
this. Access for your healing is
granted.
>> Access for your healing is what? Granted
because this week sicknesses will be
healed.
>> Diseases will be healed.
>> Demons will be cast out.
>> Access has been granted for your
freedom.
>> The Bible says you shall know the truth
and the truth shall set you free. Even
whereas you are watching online, let me
tell you this. Access is granted.
Uh-huh. God is going to open that door
for you that no man can shut. Access is
granted. I'm talking to a lady online.
I'm saying access is granted. You've
been waiting to have a child for a long
time. Access is granted.
>> This time next year, you're going to
have a baby
>> in Jesus name. Access has been granted
in Jesus name.
>> Access has been granted because at the
name of Jesus, every knee
>> shallow
>> and every tongue
that Jesus Christ is what?
>> Lord
>> is Lord. There's nothing that should
stop you. Access is granted.
Joseph had a dream.
And that dream really blessed him and he
saw himself
exalted before his family, before his
brothers.
And even though he saw that
it did not materialize,
there are people who have been
given promises but it has not been it
has never materialized
but I want you to know that you don't
give up
instead of things getting better for
Joseph it became worse
the brothers betrayed him the brothers
sold him to Egypt he found himself in
Portifer's house and in Portifer's house
he was so blessed was blessed everything
was going very well but then something
happened that landed Joseph Joph in a
dungeon and he was in there for a long
time
and by the way it was not a nice place
but he was in a dungeon and maybe some
people are in dungeons. Some people are
in uh things were just beginning to work
out for you and they went haywire and
somebody betrayed you. Somebody said
something and things shifted and you're
in a dungeon. But I want you to know
that there is a purpose why you're in
this dungeon.
While he was in there, by the way, some
two guys came in and he was able to
reveal uh their dreams. One of them was
killed, the other one was restored. The
one who was restored,
Joseph said, "Please remember me when
you when you are lifted up. Remember
remember me." Uh and maybe sometimes you
depend on people, remember me. Uh
remember me when this happens. But the
Bible says the guy forgot him for how
long?
>> For two years.
Hello.
Two years.
But the third year, tell your neighbor,
the third year,
>> Pharaoh had a dream. Not Joseph. Pharaoh
have had a dream. Let me tell you this.
God can deposit and download dreams in
your enemy's lives.
>> Somebody just missed that. God can
download dreams
in the brains and in the minds of your
enemies
>> and they can become favorable to you in
ways you cannot imagine
>> because God is unlimited. God is
unlimited. There's nothing that can stop
him. And so Pharaoh has this dream and
he cannot remember. He cannot even
discern what it is. He saw a famine. He
saw plenty. He saw cows, uh, thin cows,
fat cows, and he didn't know what to do.
So, he's wondering who will
unveil these dreams.
This guy remembers, he says, "Yeah,
yeah, yeah, I remember." But I was in
this dungeon and there was another guy
called Joseph. And you know that the
third year
Joseph was pulled out of that dungeon.
Let me tell you this. Jesus was buried
in a dungeon. He was buried in a cave.
But on the third day,
access
granted.
>> He came out of the darkness into the
light. Let me tell you this. Your third
day is here.
>> I'm saying your third day is here.
>> Hallelujah.
You know we are finishing the month the
month of J July which is the seventh
month. All right. Today the 29th.
Today's Monday. Um so today is Monday
the first day. Then there's a Tuesday
the second day. Then there's Wednesday
the third day.
Thursday is the first
and it is the eighth month.
A new beginning.
We are completing the Sabbath. We are
entering into a new season in the month
of August.
A new door has opened.
That's why the third day, the third
year, the third season, something
special is about to shift.
>> Let me tell you this. When a season
happens, it happens.
Right now across the the the city, there
are these things called lukewarts. Have
you do you know lukew
are they around?
>> Some of you have no idea what I'm
talking
but the reason why they're around is
because it is their season. Let me tell
you that there are some things that are
going to happen this week that nobody
can stop it. It is just the season.
>> It's just the season.
Amen.
And so it is up to you to go pluck that
which God has released. Take it.
>> Take it. When revival is moving in the
earth, take it. And I'm telling you,
Joseph,
the third year after he had waited for
so long, suddenly there was a knock on
his door. Ta ta. They told him, "Pharaoh
is looking for you." The Bible says he
went and cleaned himself, shaved
himself. And he did that because Joseph
knew that his opportunity had come. I'm
telling you, prepare yourself.
>> Shave. If you need to shave, clean your
hair. Go to the saloon. Thank you,
Jesus.
>> As as your season has come,
>> something has happened in Jesus name.
>> Hallelujah.
The Bible says this in Hosea. Hosea
chapter 6 verse1 again talking about the
third day. It says this. Hosea chapter
6:1, "Come, let us return to the Lord.
He has torn us to pieces, but he will
heal us. He has injured us, but he will
bind up our wounds
after two days.
He will revive us
>> on the third day.
He will restore us."
>> Come on, somebody better give God a big
hand in Jesus name. Yes.
The third day, God will do something.
God wants to do something. And on that
day, this gentleman who had been
incapacitated
in a dungeon in darkness, the Bible says
in Genesis chapter 41, reading from
verse 14, access was granted for him.
Let me read those verses in Jesus name.
So Pharaoh sent for Joseph and he was
quickly brought from the dungeon. When
he had shaved and changed his clothes,
he came before Pharaoh. And Pharaoh said
to Joseph, "I had a dream and no one can
interpret can interpret it, but I have
heard it is said of you that when you
hear a dream, you can interpret it." "I
cannot do it," Joseph replied to
Pharaoh. But God will give Pharaoh the
answer he desires. Then Pharaoh said to
Joseph, "In my dream, I was standing on
the bank of the Nile." And then he gave
him all this story and all those things.
And then Joseph interpreted those
dreams. Now fast forward to around verse
39. The Bible says this around verse 39.
Thank you Jesus. Um then Pharaoh said to
Joseph, "Since God has made all this
known to you, there is no one so
discerning and wise as you, you shall be
now. That's where now access granted
comes in. You shall be in charge of my
palace
and all my people are to submit to your
orders.
Only with respect to the throne will I
be greater than you. So Pharaoh said to
Joseph, I hereby
access granted.
I hereby put you in charge of the whole
land of Egypt. Then Pharaoh took his
signate ring from his finger and put it
on Joseph's finger. He dressed him in in
in robes of fine linen and put a gold
chain around his neck. That's where
bling bling started.
He had heard him ride in a chariot as
his second in command. And people
shouted before him, "Make way." Thus he
put him in charge of the whole land of
Egypt. Then Pharaoh said to Joseph, "I
am Pharaoh, but without your word, no
one will lift hand or foot in all of
Egypt." Pharaoh gave Joseph the name
Zephanath Paneer, and gave him Asenath,
daughter of Portifer, priest of On to be
his wife. My friend, access.
Access.
Let me tell you this. That blessing of
Joseph is your blessing.
>> You have no idea. You're standing before
a door that is open to do so much you
cannot imagine. But this particular
access granted is a c access into
dominion. Tell your neighbor access into
dominion.
>> Access into dominion.
>> Tell the other neighbor access into
dominion. access into dominion.
>> Tell the other one who just ignored you,
access
into dominion.
>> Hallelujah.
>> And Pastor Simon, when we talk about
access into dominion is because that
door had been closed.
The Bible says in Genesis 1 26 about
dominion, if I can read that, that Adam
was actually given dominion. When God
then God said, "Let us make mankind in
our image.
in our likeness so that they may rule
over the fish in the sea and the birds
in the sky, over the livestock and all
the wild animals and over all the
creatures that move along the ground. So
God created mankind in his own image, in
the image of God he created them male
and female created them. God blessed
them and and said to them, "Be fruitful
and increase in number, fill the earth
and subdue it. rule over the fish in the
sea and the birds in the sky and over
every living creature that moves on the
ground. Then God said, I give you every
seedbearing plant. And you can keep on
reading that, but God says, I give you
dominion.
You have dominion.
Psalms 8:4 and 5. This is what the Bible
says.
What is mankind that you are mindful of
them? human beings that you care for
them. You have made them a little lower
than the angels and crowned them with
glory and honor.
Verse six, you made them rulers over the
works of your hand. You put everything
under their feet. That is called
dominion. Tell your neighbor dominion.
>> Dominion.
>> You know what that simply means, Pastor
Simon? It means that God has made us to
become kings.
Kings of dominion. Kings. These are
rulers and access has been given you to
be kings. You are kings to become kings.
You are a king. You will not be a king.
You are a king. You know you don't think
you used to be a king. You're a king.
When a cow goes to bed at night, it is a
cow. When it wakes up in the morning, it
is a cow. I'm telling you,
Thank you, Jesus.
>> But beyond the cow thing, God is saying
a king is a king.
>> So look at your neighbor and tell your
neighbor, you're a king.
>> You're a king.
>> Tell them one more time, you're a king.
>> Now since that doesn't sound very well,
just tell them, I am a king.
>> I am a king.
>> You see how that changed.
>> You know, human beings are just selfish.
>> When it is about them.
So one more time with confidence tell
your neighbor I am a king.
>> I am a king.
>> I have become a king.
>> Access has been granted to me.
>> Access has been granted to me
>> in Jesus name.
>> And you see kings rule. That's what they
do. Kings govern. That's what they do.
Kings are seated.
They rest knowing that nothing is
impossible.
>> That it can happen. And God has made you
kings. But let me tell you this because
Christians don't believe that they have
access. They are always worried about
this, worried about that, wondering will
this happen? Will God make the me? Will
God make this work for me? Let me tell
you this. You are a king.
You are a king.
If you don't believe me, let me read
Revelation chapter chapter 1 verse 6 and
7. The Bible says this.
Revelation it says and has made us to be
a kingdom. Now this one says he has made
us to be a kingdom. New King James
version if I can let me use that one. It
says it a bit slightly different. It
says and he has made us what?
>> He has made us kings and priests to his
God and father. To him be glory and
dominion forever and ever. Amen. You
have dominion. So, Joseph became a king
and nobody could move, nobody could
could shift without him. Let me tell you
this, there are some things God cannot
do on this planet without you.
And he's been waiting for you to do
them. He's been waiting for you to
decree and declare. He's been waiting
for you to stand up and say, "Thus says
the king." Elijah knew that so well. and
Elijah the Bible says it shall not rain
for three years and a half unless I say
so
that is a king speaking I'm saying that
is a king speaking
>> that is a king who understands that
access has been granted let me tell you
this that job you have been looking for
has already been granted
>> that business
God has already declared it will
flourish
>> it will thrive in Jesus name
>> access has
granted in Jesus name.
>> Hallelujah. Why? Because you are in
Christ. You are in Christ. You know
there are some places when you go with a
vitz my friend they will stop you at the
barrier. They will check your car.
They will look at you suspiciously.
Then same guy you go home and then you
come back with a prao.
They will not check you. Access granted.
You just drive in. But what changed?
>> The car. You didn't change. Let me tell
you this. When you enter the car called
Jesus,
>> when you enter the car called in Christ,
>> it doesn't matter who you are.
The moment they see the car, the moment
they see the name of Jesus, the barriers
just open up and you go in in the name
of Jesus and God is saying access
granted. What can stop you? What can
stop you? What can stop you?
You know, Pastor Simon has been flying
quite a bit for and and yesterday he was
talking about flying and uh and the
airplane is flying and flying flying.
Hallelujah.
>> And we are flying.
But there's something special about
flying, Pastor Simon.
Usually when people go into the plane
and they are entering, imagine this is
the door they're entering. They usually
enter and they turn right.
Now, if you ever go into a plane and you
turn right, no, number one, you're going
to economy
because as far as you're concerned, you
paid for
>> economies. You're being economical. Tell
your neighbor when you're being
economical. So, you go right and they
are standing there to make sure you're
going Right.
If you ever one of these days walk into
the plane and you go left,
you're going to business class, you're
going to first class, you're going left.
Let me tell you this. One time Martha
and I, we were flying and I'm telling
you, we were flying business.
I I'm saying we were flying business.
We had been flying economy for a long
time. This time we were flying business
and I told Martha just watch. Usually
people who go to business go when left.
We entered and they told us uh let me
see your ticket. We they checked our
ticket and they ushered us because you
know they are standing like this. As we
are standing facing them they are
standing like this. So when they ushered
us in they ushered us where? Yes,
>> they are right. But our what?
>> Our left. And let me tell you this.
Access was granted. But let me tell you
this. One of the things that had not
changed was our mind.
We're in first class, but we are acting
like economy. Our mind
is completely an economy.
In that place, I'm telling you, you're
treated. You're treated so well. H but
you know you you you you you're just
feeling that I should not be here.
Then they bring you juice.
Hallelujah. Then they asking you what
else can we do for you in economy?
Nobody tells you what to do.
And I'm I'm I'm I'm saying we are we are
in that plane. It is just a nice plane
and we are seated in compartments. Ma is
looking at me. She's on that side me.
I'm looking at her. and and and we're
just looking everything is just w
let me tell you this God is giving you
access and all you'll be saying is w
I'm telling you it was an experience and
a half you know you press things you
have a screen for yourself
you are watching movie with
headphones
and this this was a long a long journey
so I'm in that plane I'm in that plane
we're going going going after we they've
brought us some food n finished and then
I turned and I saw a colleague in that
first class in that business classala
I'm wondering how How did he manage to
do that?
How did he manage to do that?
And I'm sitting and it is a long journey
and I'm just sitting
with my cat.
So you start checking where where did
they press? So you're checking you
checking. I'm checking. I said since I
cannot see my ignorance will keep me
sitting down and fly the do you know I
would have flown the whole way without
sleeping until I had to share my
ignorance. I told the attendant excuse
me and this is what I said um I pointed
at the guy.
I said also me
tell your neighbor who
so she comes so simply and presses
another thing and suddenly my seat moved
my seat moved.
I said just keep pressing this thing
this your this thing is just going and
so I I I did not want to try anything. I
waited for her to go away.
So if there was an accident in that
place, I'll be doing it. So I fined that
thing and I started going I fed again.
It went I then I said I I need to finish
another one so that I can come back
because I can qua there
something is about to happen to you.
>> Hallelujah.
Tell your neighbor, I am about to go
left.
>> I am about to go left.
>> Access.
>> Come on, somebody better give God a big
hand and tell him thank you.
But you see, Pastor Simon, after that
experience, the next time we flew
business, now I knew,
you know, once you have known, don't go
back to your ignorance.
Jesus died 2,000 years ago.
>> Jesus rose from the dead.
>> But Pastor Kini, let me tell you this.
It is not a sin to be ignorant.
And so try if you make mistakes, it's
okay. Try praying. If you pray for so
long and suddenly you check your watch
and it is just 3 minutes that have
passed,
don't worry. Access is still granted.
Keep going. Keep going. Breakthroughs
will begin to happen. Things will begin
to shift. You will have dominion. Tell
your neighbor, you have dominion. You
have dominion
>> in Jesus name.
>> The Bible says you will decree a thing
and it shall be established for you.
And let me tell you this, you know,
after you have flown business class and
all those first class things, going to
economy is torture.
Tell your neighbor, "The old has passed
away.
>> The old has passed away.
>> Behold, the new has come.
>> Behold, the new."
>> And maybe you're saying, "But it is too
expensive." But let me tell you this.
Jesus paid it all.
>> All to him I own.
>> Jesus has paid for your freedom.
>> Paid for you to be a king.
>> Paid for you to have dominion.
>> It is done.
It is your mind that needs to shift. It
is your mind that needs to change. You
may have come to this service with your
head down. Let me tell you this. Walk
out of this service with your head up
>> because your miracle has come.
>> Access has been granted. Access has been
granted in Jesus name.
But let me say a few things before I tie
this message down. Let me talk about
another person who got access. But for
her access was granted into authority.
Her name is Esther.
Esther was also suffering because of her
mindset
and she was a queen. The Bible says in
Esther chapter 2 verse1 17, if I may
read that very quickly, Esther had found
favor with the king.
Esther chapter 2:1 17. I believe it's
verse 17. Now the king was attracted to
Esther more than to any of the other
women. And she won his favor and
approval more than any of the other
virgins. So he set a royal crown on her
head and made her queen instead of
Vashi. Now remember this is an orphan
girl. Now she has a crown on her head.
But even though there was a crown on her
head, her mind did not shift
until Modi had to talk to her.
Esther 4:14, Modi starts talking to her
and says, "Change your mind. You are the
queen. You have authority. Access to
authority has been given to you." It
says, "Esther, for if you remain silent
at this time, relief and deliverance for
the Jews will arise from another place.
But you and your father's family will
perish. And who knows but that you have
come to the royal position for such a
time as this.
The Bible says in the next verse then
Esther sent his reply to Modi. Go gather
all the Jews who are in Susa and fast
for me. Do not eat or drink for three
days night or day. I and my attendants
will fast as you do. When this is done,
I will go to the king even though it is
against the law. and if I perish, I
perish. So Modi went away and carried
out all Esther's instructions. Next
verse, um the Bible says this, I think
it's chapter 5. If we can just go there,
on the third day, look at your neighbor,
there's a third day.
>> Oh, come on. Tell your neighbor there's
a third day.
>> You see, the third day is a resurrection
day. And I want you to know that revival
is here. On the third day, Esther put on
her royal robes and stood in the inner
court of the palace in front of the
king's hall. The king was sitting on his
royal throne in the hall facing the
entrance.
When he saw Queen Esther standing in the
court, he was pleased with her and held
out her to her the gold scepter that was
in his hand. So Esther approached and
touched the tip of the scepter. Then the
king asked, "What is it, Queen Esther?
What is your request? Even after half
the kingdom it will be given to you.
What had just happened the third day
access was granted. I will not go to the
story of what happened but one of the
person who was really um creating chaos
for the Israelites was a guy called
Hammon. Tell your neighbor Hammon.
>> I tell your other neighbor Hammon.
>> Of course don't worry if there's
somebody from Kuwi they will say a man.
But I'm telling you just say Ham. H.
>> Hallelujah.
This guy was a problem. But you know the
rest of the story. Let me tell you this.
Hmon may have the authority, but God has
given you access.
>> God has given you access.
>> No weapon that is fashioned against you
will prosper.
>> Hmon may be plotting right now in Jesus
name. He may be doing all kinds of
things. But let me tell you this.
Because the king has given you access.
He's going to give you an upper hand
>> in the name of Jesus.
>> And for sure you know the story. Hammond
later got hanged and he was put down.
That enemy was finished. But you know
Pastor Kennedy, Hammon had already sent
out letters using the king's signate
ring. And he had already sent out orders
that the Jews should be destroyed. The
letters had already gone out.
nothing could stop it because the the
the letters were signed. There was a
signate ring that had signed it. And so
Esther got very worried. Even though she
was now queen, Hammon had died. She was
still scared to death what was going to
happen to the Jews. So chapter 8, which
we're talking about a new beginning.
Chapter 8, something happened. The Bible
says this that he she had to be granted
access to authority. Pastor Simon,
Joseph was granted access for dominion.
Esther was granted authority, access for
authority. And so the Bible says the
same day, King Zak gave Queen Esther the
estate of Hammon. In other words, Jesus
said, "I give you authority over all the
power of the enemy."
In that same day, King Zakus gave Queen
Esther the state of Hammon, the enemy of
the Jews. And Modi came into the
presence of the king, for Esther had
told how he was related to her.
The king took off what?
A signate ring. Remember, Joseph was
also given what? A signate ring. The
king took off his signate ring which he
had reclaimed from Hmon and presented it
to Modi. And Esther appointed him over
Hammon's estate. Let me tell you this,
God has given you dominion.
>> But look at verse three. Esther again
pleaded with a king. Now this is very
interesting pastor Simon because the
mind takes time to shift. Uh Esther is
still pleading. Kings don't plead.
Hello. Esther again pleaded with the
king falling at his feet and weeping.
She begged. Can you see that she's
begging? She's a queen.
I'm talking to somebody right now. I say
stop begging.
You have authority.
>> Hmon has died.
>> Satan was defeated. You are over his
estate.
>> But Queen Esther's mind has not shifted.
Esther again pleaded with the king,
falling at his feet and weeping. She
begged him to put an end to the evil
plan. She's begging the king. She's
begging the king. Now listen what the
king did.
Look at the next verse. Then the king
extended the gold scepter to Esther and
she arose and stood before him. If it
pleases the king, she said, and if he
regards me with favor and thinks it it
it the right thing to do, and if he is
pleased with me, let an order be written
over ruling the dispatches that Ham son
of Hammedatha the Agagite devised and
wrote to destroy the Jews in all the
king's provinces. For how can I bear to
see disaster fall on my people? How can
I bear to see the destruction of my
family? Now listen to King Zakus. This
is what I want you to get. King Zaxus
replied to Queen Esther and to Modi the
Jew. Because Hammon attacked the Jews, I
have given his estate to Esther and they
have impaled him on the pole. He said,
"Now write."
I like this. He says, "Now write another
decree.
The devil may have said you will be
barren the whole life. God is saying
write another decree.
Write another decree.
Don't let the first decree go because it
has my signature on it.
>> He said write another decree. Now write
another decree in the king's name in
behalf of the Jews as seems best to you
compose it.
I'm not going to dictate it. You compose
it. Huh? You compose it. You decide
whether you're going to go right or
left. You compose it.
Don't don't don't don't wait for God to
say, "Oh, it is my will. It is my will,
my friend." Tell God what your will is.
Tell God what your will is.
You know the king.
Hello. And she's the one who who needs
to be.
I'm telling you
now. Write another decree in the king's
name on behalf of the Jews as seems best
to you. And seal it. Go back and seal
it. Just go back into that verse. Verse
seven. And seal it with a king's signate
ring. For no document written in the
king's name and sealed with his ring can
be revoked.
>> Hallelujah. Can be revoked. The Bible
says in the next verse, at once the
royal secretaries were summoned on the
23rd of the third month, the month of
Sivan. They wrote out all Modcia's
orders to the Jews and to the satraps to
the governors and the nobles of the 127
provinces
stretching from India. This is the first
time India is mentioned in the Bible.
Hallelujah.
From India to Kush. Kush is Ethiopia. So
that whole region uh these orders were
written in the script of each province
and the language of each people and also
to the Jews in their own script and
language. Moria wrote in the name of the
king Zaxis sealed the dispatches with a
king signate ring and sent them by the
mounted Koreas who rode fast horses
especially bread for the king. Let me
tell you this the king also sponsored
how the message would go.
>> Hallelujah.
But pastor Simon, you know something?
Though access has been given to
believers,
though they have dominion,
they have not known that they supposed
to decree themselves. They're supposed
to write. Let me ask you because I'm
about to pray. What are you going to
write this week and cancel the decree of
the enemy
>> and say this is what Hammond said
cancel? I'm doing I'm doing a new
decree. I'm putting it in writing. I
will put the signaturing, the name of
Jesus on this decree. And I'm going to
reverse everything the devil has
purposed in my life and only what God
has desired and what I desire. And now
I'm in agreement with God. This is what
is going to happen. What is this? Or are
you still going to sit and say, "Oh God,
I'm waiting for you. Oh God, I'm
pleading. If you have favor on me,
please do." God is saying, "Write it
down.
>> Write it down.
Write it down.
This is where revival be comes because
at dominion at dominion we became kings.
At authority
we bring forth the kingdom.
And God is waiting for you to bring
forth the kingdom. It's where you write
is where you decree. Is where you
enforce.
Tell your neighbor the walls of Jericho
are about to come down.
You see, I believe some things are
changing. Pastor Simon uh has been
writing and counseling things and and
saying that revival uh Nairobi will the
the epicenter. Thank you Jesus
>> of revival in Jesus name.
>> That is writing and decreeing and then
putting the signaturing and said it's
going to happen. Uh-huh. And so we are
speaking to you now even in the
the diaspora wherever you are.
Rewrite what the devil wrote about you.
>> If the devil said you'll be poor until
you die, that's okay. He wrote it. But
now write another decree.
>> Write another decree. Just look at your
neighbor. Tell your neighbor, I am
writing another decree.
>> I am writing another decree.
>> Hallelujah. Amen.
>> One time there's a young a family who
came to my office and the boy um the the
young boy and the sister and when they
were about to leave I asked the young
man, "What do you want me to pray for
you about?" He was young,
"What do you want me to pray for you
about?" And I was expecting him to say,
"Pray for my exams. Pray that I may just
pass."
Then he said, "Pray for me that I may
grow taller than my mom.
Now pastor Kinito when you receive a
prayer request like that and you know
very well number one the mother is short
and then the guy is also short is
shorter. How are you going to pray for
him?
Hello.
How are you going to pray for him?
You're going to say it is the Lord's
will for you to be short.
Shan, it is not going to happen. It is
not. Just just accept your shortness.
But you know, I took this boy
seriously because maybe people are just
pushing pushing him all the time that
he's short. He's short. And it was
getting to him. He says, "Maz, I can
just be taller and I'll sort these guys
up."
So I lay my hand on his head. I said in
the name of Jesus Christ I decree that
you'll be tall in Jesus name. Amen. We
left it at that. Now other guy cannot
get told just immediately
because if he did things would happen.
But let me tell you this.
A year later, two years later,
to date, that boy is taller than the
mother.
I'm saying that boy is taller than the
So tall. You know sometimes you reach a
stage and say by the way we we did not
give God a place to cup it
because the guy can continue
going uh we didn't say father make him
tall but Jehovah God make sure he
reaches just 6' 2 in
you know let me say something
we are writing we are decreeing this
this prayer the sevenfold prayer request
yesterday a little girl came uh during
the coonia And she had this the card
with her. I think pastor Susan had given
it to the children. This this child
about 5 years old. She comes and gives
me her card. And of course we were not
giving cards so that we could get them.
But she gives me the card. And I I gave
it back to her and I said, "No, this is
for you to keep." Then she turns back
and says, "Uh-uh, I want you to keep
it." So I took it and I kept it. So
during the office, I went I just wanted
to check her prayer request. And it is
written in the handwriting of children.
The first request apple number one.
I want my mother to be a billionaire.
You know, I looked at that statement. I
say
But you see when she wrote that request,
she was not writing for my opinion.
She was addressing it to God.
I want to tell that mother wherever she
is
things will shift in her life
that she does not know what just
happened to her
and she'll be wondering how am I just
getting all these favors? How am I just
becoming a billionaire? There's like a
little girl who believed in a mighty God
and wrote her decree down.
Then I went I scrolled another another
but I think the third one the third
request she wrote there. I want God to
give us a big mansion
maybe wherever she is.
Tell your neighbor the Lord will enlarge
you.
But write it down.
>> That is called authority.
That is why things can
things can go haywire for you and you
think you have a lot of power but
authority can stop you because somebody
will say it is written.
What have you written? Because the devil
can stop you with his power. But when
you come with authority and say it is
written,
things stop. It is written. They come
with an injunction. It is written.
But let me tell you this, many
Christians do not know how to put that
authority into effect. So the power of
the devil is just hitting you, hitting
you. Pull out that paper and tell the
devil. Pull out that Bible and tell the
devil. Speak that word and tell the
devil, "It is written.
>> It is written.
It is written my way of going into this
cycle of problems. It is written. It is
finished. If the sun sets you free,
>> you're free indeed. And put it on that
cycle of your family cycle challenges of
your family and just cross then says
from today onwards the cycle is broken.
>> Hallelujah.
>> And if you're short and you'd like to be
tall, I'm telling you,
you can be tall.
I'm particularly not talking to anybody
and fur you know I'm not talking about
you
for you're just the right size.
>> Amen.
I'm right the right side. Uh you know
just the right size. Uh hallelujah.
I'm about to pray.
I was going to talk about John the
Apostle, but I'm going to just mention
it in passing because God had given him
access and I know the other speakers
will come. We'll begin to just open it
up for me today. I was opening the door
for you. The Bible says in Revelation 4
verse one, John the Apostle in an island
stuck there. But then suddenly something
happened. The Bible says, "After this, I
looked and there before me was a door
standing
open in heaven. And the voice I had
first heard speaking to me like a
trumpet said, "Come up here, and I will
show you what must take place after
this." At once. Tell your neighbor,
access is at once.
>> Access is at once.
>> It is starting now.
>> It is starting now. Don't don't don't
sit there and says, "I hope this thing
will happen for me in September." Uh-uh.
Now,
>> I'm talking to somebody. I'm saying your
now is here.
>> I'm saying your now is here.
>> I'm talking to the Elizabeth in this
church today. If you're an Elizabeth,
I'm saying to you, access is open for
you right now.
>> Can I have the Elizabeth standing up? Uh
Or maybe you're called Beth. Beth Beth
or Betty. We just talking about the same
thing.
Hello.
Oh, you're Betty. Uh, access is now.
Now, you know, sometimes when I say
those kinds of names, you know,
sometimes God just allows you to pox
yourself in some of the people's things.
I'm talking about somebody who needs to
pox himself in that miracle right now.
pox himself among the bets, among the
Elizabeth.
Ah, just pox yourself in it.
I'm surprised that some men are standing
up. How can you
Just tell your neighbor pox
>> poxh
tell your neighbor I have pokeed myself
>> I have ped myself
>> into that miracle
>> my at once is here
>> my now is here
>> my suddenly is here
>> I am unstoppable in Jesus name
>> the door is open before me
>> the door is
I'm stepping in.
>> I'm stepping in.
>> Beth or no Beth?
>> Beth or no Beth.
>> Elizabeth or no Elizabeth?
>> Elizabeth or no Elizabeth.
>> My second name is Elizabeth.
>> Come on, somebody better give God a big
hand.
Amen.
Because while you're standing, we are
now about to pray.
>> Hallelujah.
>> We're now about to pray.
The word Beth means a house.
So when we talk about Ellie, Ellie means
God. Elisa Beth
uh like Bethl. Bethl means the house of
>> of God. Somebody is about to enter into
the house of God.
>> Access is granted.
Access is granted.
And that access is granted for
revelation because access was granted
for Joseph that was dominion. Access was
granted for Esther that is authority for
John. Access was granted for revelation.
What your eyes have not seen, you will
see.
see. I'm now talking to you.
What your eyes have not seen, you will
see. Hallelujah. What your ears have not
heard, you will hear. What your heart
has not conceived, you will conceive.
>> Tell your neighbor, I'm becoming
pregnant right now.
>> I'm also talking to the man. Tell tell
the man next to you, I'm becoming
pregnant.
>> In the name of Jesus Christ.
>> I'm conceiving. Tell your neighbor, I'm
conceiving. I'm conceiving.
>> I'm conceiving revival.
>> I'm conceiving.
>> I'm conceiving breakthrough.
>> I'm conceiving right now.
>> I'm conceive right now.
>> In the name of Jesus Christ.
>> Tell your neighbor, "Tomorrow."
>> Tomorrow.
>> If my shape changes,
>> my shape changes.
>> It's because I'm pregnant.
>> I'm also talking to the man.
>> It's not about eating too much. Tell
your neighbor, I will not be eating too
much.
I'm receiving revelation.
>> I'm receiving revelation.
>> What your eyes have not seen, you're
going to see.
>> I'm telling you, something good is about
to happen to you.
>> Miracles are coming your way.
And John saw what he had never seen
before.
And the Lord says, "Come. I will show
you what is about to happen. I will show
you
in this revival season.
God has been waiting for you. And he's
prepared a table for you because God
wants to show you. God wants to reveal
himself to you. God wants to reveal
himself aresh in your life." The Bible
says, "If my people who are called by my
name will humble themselves and pray and
seek my face and turn from their wicked
ways, I will hear from heaven. I'll
forgive their sins. I will heal their
land." God is releasing access to
dominion. He's releasing access to
authority. He's releasing access to
revelation.
And you're going to see things that you
have never seen before because you're
going to see yourself in a new level.
You're going to see yourself where
you've never stepped before.
Access
granted.
granted. Why don't you take a moment
just begin to pray and thank God for
these three levels?
The access to dominion,
the access to authority. Write it down.
Access to revelation. Forget the former
things. Do not dwell on the past.
Behold, I'm doing a new thing. What is
this that you want to see God do? What
is this door
that you thought was closed? Tonight, we
are telling you the door is open.
Take a moment
before the Lord and thank him. Thank you
for what he's going to do this week
starting tonight. Thank you for the at
once miracle that is about to happen to
you. The suddenly miracle that is about
to happen to you tonight. This pastor
has just opened the door into this
revival season.
And like Pastor Simon has been saying
and decreeing and declaring, you can
count on it that God will make it
happen. Nothing that is said on this
pulpit will fall down empty. As the word
of God goes out, it will come back
fulfilled. Begin to believe God when you
go home. Write down the decrees that you
want to completely reverse what the
enemy purpose in your life. reverse them
by writing the opposite. Yes. Because
this week as you keep coming with that
request,
we are going to say, "It is written.
>> It is written." And then we're going to
send angels. They're the ones who are
going to run and dispatch that word.
They're going to run into the future and
bring it into the present.
They're going to go into the past and
close everything that the devil had
purposed for you. Yesterday is locked.
The future is open. Today is accessible.
I bless the Lord. Bless the Lord.
Keep praying because I'm about to pray
and decree God's word for us today.
Thank you Jesus. Worship him. I don't
know if you have a song as I prepare to
pray and even as God's people are
praying.
[Music]
Yes, Lord. Yes, Lord.
>> The Holy Spirit is here. Holy Spirit,
come.
Holy Spirit, come.
Come. Holy Spirit.
>> Come. Holy Spirit.
>> Come. The Holy Spirit
come, come Lord.
>> Thank you, Holy Spirit.
>> Oh,
welcome, Holy Spirit. Welcome.
[Music]
I'm being good.
No sh
[Music]
>> Holy Spirit.
Holy Spirit,
you open the grave
so that Jesus would walk out of that
grave.
You're opening our graves
that we may walk out of those graves,
out of those limitations,
out of those bounds,
and enter into the bounty of Jehovah,
the freedom of Jehovah. Enter into our
dominion.
Enter into our authority.
Enter into our revelation.
Come Holy Spirit.
May this revival be ignited
and triggered in us at an individual
level,
at a family level,
at a church level,
at a community level,
at a city level.
This nation is ripe for revival.
>> This nation is ripe for revival and is
starting with me. It's starting with us.
I'm talking to somebody right now.
As you have stepped
into that Elizabeth position I was
talking about. As we are standing into
that position,
God is about to put together your house.
>> God is about to establish your house on
a rock.
>> And the rock.
Yes. Come on, let's give God a big hand.
Yes.
Established on a rock.
And even when it rains, when the wind
blows,
>> no matter what happens, your house will
be intact.
>> It is built
>> on the rock. That is what it means to be
in Christ.
>> For if anyone is in Christ, he is a new
creation. The old has passed away.
Behold, a new has come. Something new
has come to you. Something new has come
to you. I'm saying something new has
come to you. Thank you, Holy Spirit.
Amen.
So, just lift up your hand because God
wants as you're lifting those hands,
you're also receiving. So, God wants you
to receive a download from heaven. Just
lift those hands up because you're
you're surrendering to the go to the
Lord Almighty.
So Lord, as we open this week of
revival,
we are lifting our hands. It's like a
cup. It's like a basket before you. It
is like a cup. The Bible says, "The Lord
anoints our head with oil. Our cup
overflows." So lift up that hand because
your cup, your basket,
your container is going to overflow. It
doesn't matter what the devil has said.
It doesn't matter what circumstances
have pulled you down, but now you're
lifting up your container. You're
lifting up that basket and saying,
"Father, fill this basket. Fill this
basket." By lifting up your hands,
you're also surrendering those things
that are not of God.
>> You're saying, "God, take this from me.
Take this from me. Take that decree of
the enemy from me. I'm going to write a
new one. Take that decree from my family
members
>> who said I could not make it.
>> Take it.
>> Take that decree where sickness says it
will not leave me.
>> Take it away
>> because Lord, now my cup is ready to
receive.
>> Is ready to receive. So lift up those
hands because I'm going to ask the Holy
Spirit to fill your cup right now. The
Holy Spirit to fill that basket because
revival starts with you. I'm going to
count from seven to one. Just lift up
that basket and by the time I reach one,
a move of the Holy Spirit will just fill
this place, fill those online.
Seven, just be still. Let this spirit
come. Six.
Thank you, Holy Spirit.
Five.
Thank you, Jesus.
Four.
Lift up that cup. Three.
Lift up that cup. Two,
lift up that cup. One.
Holy Spirit, come. Fill our baskets
starting
now.
Hallelujah.
It's being poured.
It's being poured in your cup.
It's being filled.
Your basket is being filled.
And begin to decree. What do you want
that the Holy Spirit to fill your basket
with? What is it? Begin to tell him.
Tell him because he will fill. He'll
fill. Decree it. Declare it. You have
dominion. You have the name that is
above every name. Hallelujah. Some of
you are going to receive spiritual gifts
that you did not have. Yes, some of you
are going to manifest new fruit. The
fruit of joy, that fruit of laughter.
Yes, in his presence there is fullness
of joy. Yes, relinquish the sin. Take it
away, but receive the presence of God.
Oh yes, I can sense it. Holy Spirit is
here. Holy Spirit is here. Oh,
somebody's being filled with joy.
Somebody's being filled with joy. Sorrow
is leaving you. Sorrow and sighing are
fleeing away.
But it's being replaced with joy.
The garment of joy is coming upon you.
The cup of restoration, celebration
is filling you right now. Oh, Holy
Spirit, thank you. Holy Spirit, thank
you. Yes. Sorrow is going. Sorrow is
going. Morning may last for the night,
but joy comes in the morning. Your
morning has come. Your season of
restoration has come. Your season of
revival has come.
The Lord is taking you out of the
dungeon
into the palace.
Into the palace.
Oh my God.
Thank you for that favor.
And today is just the first day.
By the third day, you'll revive us.
By Thursday, things will so much
accelerate.
We will not be able to hold it. But
today, we have received the first the
appetite.
The main course is coming. We have
received the appetite.
If you're receiving the appetite, you
better say, "I receive it."
>> I receive it. I am receiving it.
>> I am receiving it.
>> It is mine.
>> It is my portion.
>> Given to me by the Lord.
>> I am in Christ.
>> I am sitting in Christ.
>> I'm resting in Christ.
>> And in Christ
>> and in Christ
>> access
>> is granted.
>> Now give God a big hand and tell him
thank you.
Amen.
Now give him another big big hand.
Tell him thank you.
Come on somebody.
[Music]
[Applause]
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on somebody.
Come on somebody.
[Applause]
Glory.
Come on, somebody.
Hallelujah.
>> Hallelujah.
Let me tell you this before we are
dismissed and released. You maybe have
heard all I've said and in your heart
you're saying, you know, pastor, you're
saying all those things, but
I have never given my life to Jesus.
I've never even stepped into that door.
Let me tell you this. The reason why our
ushers are here, Pastor Kin is here, and
our deacons are here.
And you want somebody to agree with you
by writing the decree down.
Writing it down.
May you find that moment to come and
say, "I just like to come. Even if I
don't have anything to say, I just want
to bring in myself.
And if you feel like,
this is your moment,
Cina, let's sing that song one more
time. We'll just give those people an
opportunity uh or somebody else who just
wants something written so that it is
written down or for your records that
this week the Lord will make it happen
and then I'll release us. So give me
just a moment for those who need to just
come to come
Cina.
[Music]
What?
No sh
[Music]
you What is
>> in my
[Music]
Shul
pushing
[Music]
Thank you,
Father. We bless you for an amazing
evening.
And now Lord, even as I prepare to
release your people,
I know that the Holy Spirit is working
in an amazing way.
You have opened the door.
Access
granted
for Joseph. Access was granted for
Esther. Access was granted for the
Apostle John.
access was granted.
May we carry that message into this
night
because God we are more than conquerors.
And now Lord
before I blessed these people I want to
say father that because they have
invested their time their time was not
wasted they have invested their time in
this service. Those who are watching us
online, they have invested their time.
And I pray that indeed because of their
investment,
it will acrue interest
>> the interest of the kingdom of God and
that it will be multiplied to them in
ways they cannot imagine.
>> Pressed down,
>> shaken together and running over shall
be given to them.
So Lord, I say thank you
and thank you Lord for the
response team that is here, our deacons,
Pastor Kini that even as they continue
standing here that people will be able
to come and talk to them.
So thank you for hearing us, Lord. I I
really appreciate that you gave me this
opportunity to open the week and cause
the floodgates to begin to flow through.
In Jesus name we pray. Why don't we give
God a big thank you?
Amen.
Okay.
Now, by the way, when I was praying,
there's this name that kept coming. I
don't know why. So, I may not you may
not need to come, but there's a person
called Alfred.
I don't know why that name came. There's
a person called Alfred. Whatever it is,
please connect with this response team.
Whatever it is, the Elizabeth's just
know this. Access granted.
>> And those who ps to themselves,
including Pastor Ken,
>> accessed
>> rented. Amen.
>> Amen.
>> Remember, where do you want to turn
>> in Jesus name?
>> Amen.
So that there's an Alfred. Maybe that
Alfred is online.
Whoever it is, connect with us.
Something special is about to happen to
you. And let me tell you this. You
better be here tomorrow.
>> I want to ask my sister to come up here
one minute.
She has invested her time with us.
Hasn't
she done an amazing an amazing ministry
for us?
Amen.
Amazing ministry.
So I want to say to you, I don't know
these doors
you're
you're planning to open, but I want to
tell you this.
Because of your ministry tonight,
because of your service to your Lord
tonight,
the Lord is saying some unprecedental
things that are just about to happen in
your life.
And those things are not man-made.
They're not pushed by people.
They are pushed and accessed by court.
Something good is coming your way.
And if you have never walked into a
plane and gone left,
I want you to know you're about to go
left.
Left.
Ah, you're about to go left.
Uh,
and this trip will be paid for.
You and your husband paid for.
>> Access granted.
Access granted.
So go home and write it down so that it
is printed. You can either write it on
your phone or write it on paper and say
and when it happens because it's going
to happen very soon.
um
let us know and if you don't let us know
it will still happen anyway.
>> Amen.
>> So look at our sister Kamanzi and say
access granted.
>> Access granted.
>> Turn to the left.
>> That's your portion.
Amen.
And uh and when it happens, remember
what I told you about how we try to
adjust our brains. Um so don't don't
think economy when you're in first
class. Hallelujah. But I want to also
release a blessing because has this
grace of releasing the blessing.
We want to release a blessing into your
ministry. a blessing that will will will
by the way
uh the name New York has just entered my
head
>> because that's where you're heading
that's where you're heading
New York International Airport
New
And if you if you need travel agents who
can plan for you,
but it will be paid for.
Receive that just because you came.
Release that blessing. Favor.
Favor.
stretch your hand as we bless her.
Father,
[Music]
sometimes Lord, your servants come to
minister to us and they do it by faith.
And I know my sister may have had many
other schedules
through the day to be here and then get
back home. But Lord, you have seen it
fit for us to decree and to declare this
amazing word because father
this your servant is about to travel
internationally.
>> Doors are opening for her
>> Father, we release that into her spirit.
We release her that in that into her
mind that father she doesn't go need to
check her bank account because your bank
account is access granted
>> and you're about to do something awesome
something amazing
and whatever ministry you have for her.
Maybe it is not just a ministry. Maybe
it's just a holiday, a vacation, a place
for her to rest. But Father, in the
mighty name of Jesus, we now seal it. We
declare that it will happen. and the
devil will not tamper with it
>> in any way. And she'll come back
refreshed. She'll come back anointed.
>> She'll come back to release even more
ministry
>> for the kingdom of God.
>> So we release this blessing to you now
in the name of the Father and in the
name of the Son and in the name of the
Holy Spirit. And God's people say amen.
>> Amen. Amen.
Bless you.
Hallelujah.
Amen.
What he has just told me is this.
You know, in a team, you cannot just be
in a team and just live like that. The
word team, if you remove the M, what do
you have?
>> So tell your neighbor after this,
>> there is T.
>> Tell your neighbor, come for tea.
>> Come for tea. Come for tea, my people.
>> Now for those watching online, uh the
tea is in Parkland's Baptist Church. Uh
the tea in your house, you can take tea.
But I want to tell you, those of you
online in the diaspora, that what is
happening here in Parkland's Baptist
Church is going to overflow into your
life in ways you cannot imagine. Ways
you cannot imagine.
So lift up your hands as I release this
blessing. And tomorrow, what time are we
coming?
>> 5:30 Sunday, when what time are we
>> 10.
>> 6.
I know some of you are going to Kesha
that Saturday
but come the service itself begins at
10:00 but you are getting seats if you
don't want to get a back seat come Ali
now I want to also give you homework
let's continue praying for Israel mon he
comes and all the artists this week and
all the speakers let's also pray for his
ministry and concert that will be on the
10th of August. I want to decree and
declare this that concert will be sold
out.
>> Will be sold out.
Sold out in Jesus name.
So you better get your tickets.
And Pastor Simon is willing
to pay for somebody for 20,000.
Hallelujah.
But that promise is conditional.
You need to have memorized
the book of Philippians chapter 2.
Once Simon knows you have memorized it.
20,000
I'm a lia
I know what some of you will do you will
come with your Bibles pastor I have
memorized
but pastor Simon will will make that
happen
which
>> which language
English,
>> but that concert will be sold out.
>> So, continue praying, continue
believing. We want to see a great
shaking in this city
>> for the kingdom of God. Amen.
>> Stretch your hands as I bless us
>> and may you reach home well.
>> Father, as I release this blessing, I'm
releasing to to those who are here. I'm
releasing to those who are watching
online. And Father, we are decreeing and
declaring, I decree in that name that is
above every name. And I declare unto you
tonight, may the Lord bless you.
>> Amen.
>> May the Lord make his face to shine upon
you.
>> Amen.
May the Lord be gracious to you.
>> May the Lord do you good
>> this week of revival.
>> May the Lord open doors for you that no
man can shut.
>> Amen.
>> May the Lord go behind you and come
behind you.
>> May the Lord stand beside you underneath
you the everlasting arms.
>> The Lord has granted you access.
>> Now believe it.
>> Receive it.
>> Take it.
>> It is your portion.
The third day the Lord will restore you.
>> Amen.
>> The third day you'll come out of
darkness into light.
>> The third day you'll come from limited
to unlimitedness.
>> The third day you'll enter the palace
out of your prison.
>> Access granted. I bless you in the name
of the father and in the name of the son
and in the name of the holy spirit that
the angels will accompany you and bring
you home safely
>> and bring you safely back tomorrow as we
enjoy the banquet table this entire
week. So receive this blessing one more
time in the name of the father and in
the name of the son and in the name of
the holy spirit and god's beloved people
say
>> amen. Come on, let's give God a big
hand.
Amen.
Look at your neighbor. Tell your
neighbor, "Surely goodness
>> Surely goodness
>> and mercy
>> shall follow you
>> all the days of your life
>> and you
>> you shall dwell
>> in the house of the Lord
>> in his blessings
>> in his favor
>> in his favor. In his goodness,
>> in his goodness,
>> in his success,
>> in his access,
>> all the days of your life,
>> all the days of your life.
>> And there's nothing the devil can do
about it.
>> You are blessed.
>> To be a blessing.
>> to be a blessing.
>> You're favored.
>> You're favor.
>> To be favorable.
>> to be favorable.
>> You're lifted.
>> You are lifted.
>> To lift others up.
>> It is sealed.
>> The devil cannot tamper with it.
>> The devil cannot tamper.
>> In Jesus name.
>> in Jesus name.
>> Amen.
Amen.
And now may the grace of our Lord Jesus
Christ and the love of God and the
fellowship of the Holy Spirit be with us
now and forever more. Amen. Shalom.